[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals have no teeth?", "correct_answer": "Turtles", "incorrect_answers": ["snails", "Hares", "Wombats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of a 1971 Academy Award-nominated movie directed by John Schlesinger?", "correct_answer": "Sunday Bloody Sunday", "incorrect_answers": ["Monday Bloody Monday", "Wednesday Bloody Wednesday", "Thursday Bloody Thursday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word phlebo is of Greek origin, which comes from the root phlein, meaning to gush or to overflow.  What part of the body does this word refer to?", "correct_answer": "Veins", "incorrect_answers": ["Aorta", "Arteries", "Capillaries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the scary creature that was tamed in a legend about Saint Martha?", "correct_answer": "Tarasque", "incorrect_answers": ["Yomi", "Tarabon", "Sphinx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The construction of this famous building was completed on November 1st, 1800. It was designed by Irish-born architect James Hoban, who was inspired by the Leinster House in Dublin.", "correct_answer": "The White House", "incorrect_answers": ["Williams Tower", "Federal Hall", "The Chrysler Building"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT needed for skin puncture?", "correct_answer": "povidone-iodine pad", "incorrect_answers": ["Lancet", "Micro-collection device", "Gauze pad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Forrest Gump had to ask Jenny to marry him twice before she finally said yes to him.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1975 Archie Griffin became the first two-time Heisman Trophy Winner.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals multiply so quickly that in 18 months they can have over million descendants?", "correct_answer": "rats", "incorrect_answers": ["worms", "grasshoppers", "snakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what disease did former U.S. President James K. Polk die in 1849?", "correct_answer": "Cholera", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken Pox", "Malaria", "Flu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not possible to happen to water in its different states?", "correct_answer": "All of these are possible", "incorrect_answers": ["Vapor to condense into clouds", "Ice to sublimate into water vapor", "Snow to sublimate into water vapor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actresss father created The Today Show, The Wide World of Sports, Your Show of Shows(aka the Sid Caesar Show) and helped  create The Tonight Show.", "correct_answer": "Sigourney  Weaver", "incorrect_answers": ["Diane Lane", "Debbie Allen", "Jobeth Williams"]}]